Hassan Adel Shaalan

Interpreter

Email: hassanalmansory1997@gmail.com

Address: Albasrah Phone: +9647717826418 Date of birth: 05-22-1997 Nationality: iraqi

Link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hassan-alali-106a45158

OBJECTIVE

Experienced, talented, and highly organized individual seeking an Interpreter position with a highly organized company., Graduated from university of Basrah college of arts department of English and two years of experience in a company for iron trade as accountant to maintain accurate financial records.

EXPERIENCE

Basrah, Iraq May 2021 - Currently

Invigilator

VICTVS Global

- Inspector: ensure correct procedures are followed throughout examinations
- Observer: monitor candidates' behaviour throughout an examination
- **Protector**: protect hard-working, honest candidates

Basrah January 2019 - August 2021

HSE Supervisor

Elekhlas for iron trade

- Maintain daily safety meeting to illustrate the Hazards and controls of each activity.
- Work site Hazard identification during the work progress and implement the controls as Required.
- Report the unsafe act and the unsafe condition and implement the remedial work plane to Close out.
- Outline safe operational procedures which identify and take into account all relevant hazards.

Basrah May 2018 - January 2019

accountant

Barakat Al-Hassan for travel and tourism

- Answered calls, responded to emails, and spoke with clients face-to-face.
- · working on the computer to prepare visas for clients

EDUCATION

September 2017 - September 2021

College of arts department of Enlish

Basra college of Science and Technology

- study the history of English literature
- practicing the simultaneous translation and written translation in professional manner

• Exercise to listen to different dialects and tongues for different regions

Basra - 2017

High school degree

Al-Azim

SKILLS

- Customer service
- Sales
- Quick learner
- Knowledge of WAN/LAN components
- Teamwork
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills
- Digital Photography Portraits, events, real estate and sports photography

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced. BA Degree

Arabic

Advanced. Mother tongue

French

Elementary. BA courses